marquisoffashion.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

Love it? Like it? SHARE IT!

##  **Privacy** **Policy**

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

****Terms of Use  **About the Author of the site and Editorial Policy:**

The site is written and edited by:

  * Mark St. James, Author & Editor  
BA, English

We are not influenced by sponsors, stake-holders or managing personnel.  Our editors decide what collections, designers, brands, and news stories to feature on the site.  Our primary objective is to deliver top quality, relevant and captivating fashion industry news to our readership.

The Marquis of Fashion  group is committed to the principles of authenticity, accuracy, fairness, objectivity, and editorial integrity. Through our reviews of fashion lines and seasonal collections, we offer unique commentary and well formed observations on the latest trends and runway shows while maintaining the highest ethical and professional standards.  As a part of our mandate, we endeavor to bring our readership closer to the fashion world and attend fashion shows to bring readers live and up to the minute coverage from various fashion weeks.

We take journalistic integrity very seriously.  Our posts are painstakingly chosen, edited, and processed.

Articles are set apart from advertorials, advertisements, and other promotional content on the web-pages, and separate graphics and color combinations followed to make them appear easily distinguishable from news content.

We are dedicated to providing readers the highest quality material.  We strive to deliver a product with:

**Adherence to Highest Professional Standards**

  * Appropriate newsmakers, celebrities, authentic news sources, and subject experts interviewed
  * News sources appropriately quoted and news facts properly attributed to sources
  * photos and captions/footnotes provided when appropriate
  * Facts thoroughly researched and cross-checked
  * Information made available on time

**Professionally Written**

  * Well-structured write-ups written in a coherent language
  * Adherence to AP Style-book
  * Grammatical correctness
  * Choice of words, and punctuation etc.
  * Proper sentence structure with smooth transition of ideas within paragraphs as well as within the whole news
  * Inverted pyramid style followed in news-writing

Should you have any questions regarding our site, the authors or this policy, please feel to contact ushere. Thank you.

**Terms of Use:**

The Website Owner, including subsidiaries and affiliates (“Website” or “Website Owner” or “we” or “us” or “our”) provides the information contained on this website or any of the pages comprising the website (“website”) to visitors (“visitors”)(cumulatively referred to as “you” or “your” hereinafter) subject to the terms and conditions set out in these website terms and conditions, the privacy policy and any other relevant terms and conditions, policies and notices which may be applicable to a specific section or module of this website.

**Information on the Website**

While every effort is made to update the information contained on this website, neither the Website Owner nor any third party or data or content provider make any representations or warranties, whether express, implied in law or residual, as to the sequence, accuracy, completeness or reliability of information, opinions, any share price information, research information, data and/or content contained on the website (including but not limited to any information which may be provided by any third party or data or content providers) (“information”) and shall not be bound in any manner by any information contained on the website. the Website Owner reserves the right at any time to change or discontinue without notice, any aspect or feature of this website. No information shall be construed as advice and information is offered for information purposes only and is not intended for trading purposes. You and your company rely on the information contained on this website at your own risk. If you find an error or omission at this site, please let us know.

**Trade Marks**

The trade marks, names, logos and service marks (collectively “trade marks”) displayed on this website are registered and unregistered trade marks of the Website Owner. Nothing contained on this website should be construed as granting any licence or right to use any trade mark without the prior written permission of the Website Owner.

**External Links**

External links may be provided for your convenience, but they are beyond the control of the Website Owner and no representation is made as to their content. Use or reliance on any external links and the content thereon provided is at your own risk. When visiting external links you must refer to that external websites terms and conditions of use. No hypertext links shall be created from any website controlled by you or otherwise to this website without the express prior written permission of the Website Owner. Please contact us if you would like to link to this website or would like to request a link to your website.

**Specific Use**

You further agree not to use the website to send or post any message or material that is unlawful, harassing, defamatory, abusive, indecent, threatening, harmful, vulgar, obscene, sexually orientated, racially offensive, profane, pornographic or violates any applicable law and you hereby indemnify the Website Owner against any loss, liability, damage or expense of whatever nature which the Website Owner or any third party may suffer which is caused by or attributable to, whether directly or indirectly, your use of the website to send or post any such message or material.

**Warranties**

The Website Owner makes no warranties, representations, statements or guarantees (whether express, implied in law or residual) regarding the website, the information contained on the website, your or your companys personal information or material and information transmitted over our system.

**Disclaimer of Liability**

The Website Owner shall not be responsible for and disclaims all liability for any loss, liability, damage (whether direct, indirect or consequential), personal injury or expense of any nature whatsoever which may be suffered by you or any third party (including your company), as a result of or which may be attributable, directly or indirectly, to your access and use of the website, any information contained on the website, your or your companys personal information or material and information transmitted over our system. In particular, neither the Website Owner nor any third party or data or content provider shall be liable in any way to you or to any other person, firm or corporation whatsoever for any loss, liability, damage (whether direct or consequential), personal injury or expense of any nature whatsoever arising from any delays, inaccuracies, errors in, or omission of any share price information or the transmission thereof, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon or occasioned thereby or by reason of non-performance or interruption, or termination thereof.

Use of the Website

The Website Owner does not make any warranty or representation that information on the website is appropriate for use in any jurisdiction. By accessing the website, you warrant and represent to the Website Owner that you are legally entitled to do so and to make use of information made available via the website.
